acro erstmal. Ta haa!
Asuna!
Watch out!
Run, get out of here!
I don't know.
Asuna!
Mrs. Kirikai?
Sugou?
He's stable and out of danger now.
Thank goodness that said, his heart
did stop for more than five minutes.
So there's a strong chance he
suffered some degree of brain damage.
Now we don't know anything for sure yet.
But it's possible he could
have a permanent mental?
and or physical disability.
Or, worst case, he never
regains consciousness.
No!
Until he has an MRI, we won't
know the scope of the damage?
if there is any.
He'll have to be transferred to a
better-equipped facility for that.
If you follow me, I can get you
started on the paperwork. Okay.
Hello, Asuna, Suguha.
Mr. Kikuoka.
Are Kirito's parents here?
I'd like a word.
Let's go.
SHINING SOMERAL DIAMOND
Sorry, I'm late.
Isn't your mom coming?
She's still trying to find a parking spot.
She wants us to sign in and
wait for her in the lobby.
Okay.
I hope they can help him.
Do you know if he's here already?
Yeah.
The nurse on the phone said they
brought him over earlier today.
There's only one hospital in the
world that has the right equipment.
If he goes there, Kazuto
will have the best treatment.
Hi.
We're here to visit a patient.
Kazuto Kirigaya.
One moment, and I'll look him up.
Um, I'm sorry.
I have to check with my supervisor.
Please wait here.
Why wouldn't they let you see him?
They said it has to do with
the equipment they're using.
He can't help visitors
until he's recovered.
But they can't do that!
That's totally illegal! Your family!
Hospitals can't keep a
patient's family from visiting.
She's right.
This sounds fishy.
Yes, it does.
So we dug around to see
if we could find anything.
The hospital records say
he's registered as a patient,
but then I noticed
something that didn't mesh.
The ambulance transporting
him never stopped there.
That doesn't make any sense.
If they didn't take him
there, then where did they?
What does Ki-Kuoka have to say about this?
He hasn't returned any
of my calls or my emails.
And the ministry said he's been out
since yesterday on business. I bet.
That creep's totally avoiding you.
No matter how you slice it,
he's up to something suspicious.
Yeah, but the question is, what?
I don't trust him.
For all we know, he could be making Kirito
do some kind of weird VR experiment.
But how?
Kirito can't do anything
if he's unconscious.
Maybe he can, though.
What I mean is, sure,
Kirito's body can't do anything
now, but that doesn't matter,
since they have a rig
that can access his soul.
The soul translator.
What's a soul translator?
I never heard of it.
It's a new full-dive machine that can
access and interface with human souls.
A company called Rath is
the one developing it.
Whoa, hang on, Rath?
Those are the people Kazuto's
been working part-time for.
Did he tell you anything about them?
No, nothing specific, really.
He did say they were based in
Roppongi, but that's about it.
Okay, if that's where they are,
that's where we should start looking.
Actually, there might be another
way to track Kirito's location.
It's kind of a long shot, though.
What is it?
I told you about it the
other day, remember?
The app he made. This thing.
Oh, right.
His little heart monitor wait
what heart monitor i lost
the signal to him a while ago
but i have Someone tracing his
last known coordinates now who
hey yui you there yes i just
finished Analyzing all the
data i'll track the coordinates
from daddy's bio monitor now
this one is the place Where
daddy started saragaya general
hospital this one is the first
location daddy's monitor Pinged
a cell tower alba die block
three megura ward the timestamp
is 2050 on june 29th 2026
Here is daddy's predicted
route the next time he pinged
was here shirogane die block
one Minato Ward at 2110.
And last...
He pinged again at Kaigon
Block 2, Minato Ward at 2120.
And that's it.
I checked all the packets.
There have been no further pings.
He's not in Tokorozawa or Roppongi?
Yui, what's at that last address you have?
All I can tell is that it
is some sort of warehouse.
Why would they take him out there?
Minato ward
Almost there this time of night.
There ain't too much
traffic heading this way.
Thanks Klein I really appreciate you driving
us out here. Come on. Quit thanking me.
I'd do anything for you guys
Can't believe we were all having
fun in GGO the other day, and now...
Well, I just hope he's okay.
I just hope he stops getting mixed
up in weird experiments after this.
Didn't you guys say this
Wrath company was in Roppongi?
Shouldn't we be looking
for him there, too?
Actually, Sinon and the
others should be there by now.
It's so weird.
There's no info on Wrath at all.
Yui checked all the public
records, everything.
All she found was their address.
There was nothing about the
company or what they did.
The same with that soul translator thing.
If it's new tech, no
one's talking about it.
A machine that can interface with
the soul is the biggest deal ever.
You know who doesn't patent that?
Sneaky bastards, that's who. Oh, cool.
We're almost there.
That's it huh I don't
get it what's the point
of stashing kitty dude
out here by the docks?
Hey Liz we're out in
front of Rath's office now
their security's super
tight and they Wouldn't
tell us a thing oh and there's cameras all
around so we asked you
to check out the footage?
Which, as far as she could tell,
they didn't bring Kirito here.
Okay, I'll call you later.
Hey, Yui. Here, Mommy.
I just checked all the
security cameras in the harbor.
This property has a helipad over there.
Yesterday at 2120, a
helicopter took off from it.
Do you know if he was on it?
Well, I can't confirm,
but I believe he was.
Oh, my God.
They could have taken him anywhere then.
Now what?
Wait, let's not panic. Yui?
Just confirming, this is the
last place his signal showed up.
Yes, it is.
He needs treatment, so they'll have
to take him to some kind of facility.
But if they landed, Kirito's signal
should have popped up again by now.
Unless, wherever he is, is out of range.
Yes, that must be the case.
It's possible they took
him out of the country.
Say what?
It's one possibility.
It's also the most likely.
What do we do?
He could be anywhere in the world by now.
He's right.
How the heck are we going to find him?
Kirito.
Cheer up, Mommy. Have hope.
I'm trying.
When you were trapped in Alphine,
Daddy searched all over for you.
He never gave up, and
eventually he found you. I know.
Then cheer up!
Now it's your turn to search for him!
I know you'll find a clue that
will lead you straight to Daddy.
And if anyone stands in
your way, they'll be sorry.
Because nothing, no one can
sever the bond between you.
It didn't matter what dangers he faced.
Kirito never backed down.
I'll find him, if it's
the last thing I do.
Thanks for the pep talk, Yui.
You're right.
I won't give up.
That's the spirit!
Let's think for a sec here.
What do we know about Wrath?
Assuming they're the
ones who have Kirito now.
Suguha, did Kirito ever tell
you anything about them?
Anything at all?
I haven't seen him that much
lately because of his work.
We talked a bit now
and then, but not much.
You know what?
Come to think of it, he
did say something once.
Something about how that machine he was
testing was based on the Medicuboid.
They share the same tech?
I had no idea.
The Medicuboid.
I just remembered something he told me.
You know who designed the Medicuboid?
The Commander.
Akihiko Kayaba.
He laid the groundwork, but his
partner developed it for hospitals.
Yeah, in fact, she was taking care of
Heathcliff's body while he was diving.
She was his head researcher.
She helped him develop
full-dive technology.
What was her name?
Rank Kojuro, I think.
I'll run a search.
I found someone who's most
likely the person you mentioned.
Currently, she's a researcher at the
California Technological Institute.
This is her.
The university's database
details her career so far.
She's a former member of the
Shigemura Lab at Toto Institute of
Technology's Department of Electrical
and Electronic Engineering.
Wait, isn't Shigemura the
guy who made the Ogma?
Yeah, and Kayaba was one of his students.
She might know something about the STL?
And Wrath!
Wait, a floating castle?
Yeah, a castle in the
sky with numerous floors.
A hundred floors, maybe.
And each one has a town,
a forest, and a plain.
To get to the next floor,
you climb a long staircase.
And when you reach the
top, you'll find a palace.
So, what's in the palace?
I don't know.
When I was young, I used to go to
that castle every night in my dreams.
Every night, I'd climb up each staircase
and get closer to the top, bit by bit.
But then at some point, I
wasn't able to go there again.
It was just a silly dream.
I pretty much forgot all about it.
Liar.
Not again.
Hasuna Yuki?
Almost there.
You'll see the ocean turtle in a sec.
Why turtle?
Uh, see it.
Yeah, I guess it looks like one.
Looks more like a pig from here, though.
Or a pig turtle.
Wasn't there a creature like that
in the Alice in Wonderland book?
Wrath.
Dr.
Kojiro, welcome aboard.
And who is this?
This is my assistant, Mayumi Reynolds.
It's nice to meet you.
Likewise, my name is Lieutenant Nakanishi.
I'll escort you below deck.
This way, watch your step.
I need you to verify Dr.
Kojiro and her assistant, Ms.
Reynolds, for access to
Sector S3. Right away, sir.
ID verified.
I'm sorry, ma 'am.
You'll have to remove
your sunglasses for this.
Sure.
ID verified. Proceed.
Security's awfully tight here.
You'd think the middle
of the ocean was safe.
Actually, we're required to
run full body checks on guests.
But you've gone through three metal
and explosives detectors already, so...
Welcome to Wrath, Doctor.
Ki-Kuoka.
Sorry, Lieutenant Colonel.
You look comfy.
Where's your uniform?
Um, sir, I'll be on the
comms if you need me.
I've been stuck out here in the middle
of the ocean for about a month now.
I can't always be in a uniform,
or a suit for that matter.
I can't begin to tell you how happy
I am to finally have you here.
I was starting to worry my
persistence scared you away.
Just because I'm here doesn't
mean I've agreed to anything.
Fair enough.
But before you decide anything,
you should know you're one of three people
whose skills are crucial to this project.
And now, you're all here.
Congratulations.
Well, well, look who it is.
Don't tell me he roped
you in on this too, Higa.
What do you think?
Of course he did.
Honestly, I'm stoked to be here.
I'm carrying on the legacy
of Shigemura Lab. I swear.
You haven't changed a bit, have you?
Well, who's the third
person you mentioned?
Unfortunately, I can't introduce you now.
But don't worry.
In a few days, I'll show...
Mr.
Kikoka, you'll take us to him.
Now.
Asuna, I...
What are you doing here?
She sent me an interesting email.
An organization called Wrath is developing
a machine called the Soul Translator.
It's based on the Medicuboid,
the medical full-dive rig you
designed the technology for.
Kazuto Kirigaya was testing
this new machine but
he disappeared and I need
your help to find him.
Kazuto Kirigaya I was
in the old Sao server
and I met Kayaba's digital ghost there.
We spoke he gave me a
program called the Seed do
you know it if you do I'd
like to get your thoughts.
If you hate him for what he did, then
just delete it and forget all about it.
It's okay, really. End it.
But if there's still a part of
you that sees VR's potential...
After Kirito disappeared,
I went through his contacts and
that's where I found your email.
If you know anything about Wrath, anything
at all, it could help me find him.
You're my last hope, Dr.
Kojiro. Help me. Please.
Sorry.
Did we surprise you?
Are you having second thoughts now about
inviting me to be on your project, Mr.
Kikwoka?
Apparently our security
wasn't thorough enough.
I know we have your assistant's
photo from the university.
They should have run a
proper check. They did.
On our way in, they scanned my
face quite a few times, in fact.
But I had her assistant's
photo in the school's
database switched with mine a while ago.
I happen to know someone who's
great at busting through firewalls.
Right now, the real Mayumi is probably
on a beach somewhere, working on her tan.
Take me to Kirito!
must be Alice to you